http://www.spelwerx.com/privacy.html

Sabbats (Seasons of the
Witch)
Spelwerx Privacy Policy
Spelwerx Privacy Policy: The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to provide you with important detailed information concerning the privacy services and policies of Spelwerx.com. Spelwerx respects the privacy of our partners and suppliers of products or services, clients, and their customers. The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to provide you with information concerning our services, the types of information we are provided by third parties or obtain ourselves through your visits to our Website, how we use that information, whether we disclose the information provided to us to others, and the options you have with regard to the use and correction of that information.
Our goal in handling personal information provided to us is to comply with applicable privacy laws worldwide and to offer users of our Website notice, choice, consent, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement with regard to personal information. Although legal requirements vary worldwide, Spelwerx's goal is to provide protection for your personal information no matter where that information is collected, transferred, or retained.
Spelwerx assumes no responsibility or liability for services that may be provided through sites bearing our partners’s and suppliers' names and trademarks and are not in the sole control of Spelwerx. Additionally, Spelwerx may provide links from our Website to the websites of third parties who may provide services to you directly or on our behalf. THE PRIVACY POLICIES OF THESE THIRD PARTY SITES MAY BE DIFFERENT FROM OUR PRIVACY POLICIES AND WILL GOVERN ANY TRANSACTIONS UNDERTAKEN ON THOSE SITES. We urge you to review the privacy policy of any site to which you are linked.
Spelwerx assumes no responsibility or liability for services that may be provided through sites bearing our partners' and suppliers' names and trademarks and are not in the sole control of Spelwerx. Additionally, Spelwerx may provide links from our Website to the websites of third parties who may provide services to you directly or on our behalf. THE PRIVACY POLICIES OF THESE THIRD PARTY SITES MAY BE DIFFERENT FROM OUR PRIVACY POLICIES AND WILL GOVERN ANY TRANSACTIONS UNDERTAKEN ON THOSE SITES. We urge you to review the privacy policy of any site to which you are linked.
Collection of Personal Information
Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, and may include but is not limited to your name, physical or email address, phone number, type of hardware or software you own, credit card details, and other information required to provide you with the product, service, or support requested. Depending on the nature of the services provided by Spelwerx to our partners or suppliers or the services provided to Spelwerx from its partners or suppliers, Spelwerx may receive personal information either from you directly or from our partner or supplier. Some of the ways Spelwerx may receive personal information include but are not limited to:
requesting information about products and services;
entering a contest or promotion;
ordering newsletter or other informational tools;
purchasing, downloading and/or registering products; and/or
signing up for additional services.
Use of Personal Information
Personal information provided to us may be transferred worldwide within Spelwerx or to third-parties providing services to Spelwerx including but not limited to across borders, from your country or collective area to other countries or collective areas around the world.
Some of the ways in which we will use the personal information provided us include:a) to take, process or deliver your order, process or obtain payment or notify you of the status of your order;
b) in connection with keys, access codes or other information as may be required to permit you to access our partners' sites to receive products, updates or services;
c) to provide it to industry and credit related organizations for security, credit or fraud prevention purposes;
d) to register your purchase with the manufacturer or service provider for warranty, technical support or similar purposes;
e) to facilitate the renewal of subscriptions for products or services;
f) to provide you with effective customer service and/or technical support;
g) to monitor service or purchasing patterns;
h) to provide you with service updates, announcements, and other product offerings;
i) to send you, with your consent, newsletters or promotional emails or undertake other promotional activities;
j) to permit you to participate in online surveys and polls, assuming you voluntarily agree to provide such information in connection with these surveys and polls; and
k) to improve Spelwerx's websites, the customer experience and any related products or services.
We will take reasonable steps to ensure any person or entity receiving personal information for the purposes described above, are obligated to protect the personal information on your behalf. By submitting your order either to our partner or to us you consent to the use of your personal information as set forth above, and to the transfer of that data to our partners or those individuals or entities we engage to provide services in connection with your transaction.
Management of Personal Information
Spelwerx tries hard to keep personal information accurate and up-to-date. If you find that your personal information is not accurate, please let us know. Spelwerx will use best efforts to investigate your concerns after we receive your inquiry and make the necessary corrections, additions and/or deletions.
Disclosure of Personal information
Spelwerx discloses your personal information directly to you upon your request; provided, however, that we may reject all or part of your request when: 1) the disclosure may harm the life, the body, the property and the other rights of yourself or the third parties, 2) the disclosure may lead the remarkable difficulties to the appropriate operation of our business or 3) the disclosure may lead a breach of the other laws and regulations.
Cookies and Web Beacons
We may use "Cookies" and other tracking technologies such as web beacons. "Cookies" are small text files that are transferred to your computer's hard disk by the website. Spelwerx's cookies are used to identify a computer or browser, not to identify specific customer traits. If you do not want cookies in your browser, you may set your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when a website attempts to place a cookie in your browser.
Web Beacons (also referred to as GIF files, pixels or action tags) help Spelwerx recognize a unique cookie on your browser. We use this tool to compile aggregate information about you, and it is not personally identifiable. This information includes IP addresses, search terms, domain names, and browser types. We use this information to track usage and other patterns on our Websites. We may share this aggregate information with our partners or service providers.
Sharing Personal Information
Spelwerx may receive personally identifiable information either from you directly or from our partner or supplier who provides us with the personal information to fulfill a service to you on their behalf. In some circumstances, personal information that Spelwerx receives from you directly may be provided to our partners or suppliers in order for them to fulfill a service to us for your benefit or directly to you. We may also provide your information in order to register your purchase with the manufacturer or service provider for warranty, technical support or similar purposes.
Spelwerx also employs other companies to provide services to us in connection with your transaction. We do use companies to process credit card payments, deliver packages, send mail, analyze data, provide marketing aid and assistance, provide customer service, and otherwise provide services to us to enable us to serve you and enhance our services. These organizations may have access to personal information as required to permit them to perform their obligations to us. Personal information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Spelwerx or its affiliates, subsidiaries, agents or partners maintain offices, and you consent to any transfer of this information outside of the country in which you reside by your use of this site.
Spelwerx may be required to respond to subpoenas, court orders or be asked to respond to other legitimate requests for your personal information from appropriate law enforcement or governmental authorities. We will not provide you with notice of such requests. In such situations, we will release personally identifiable information to third parties when we believe it is appropriate for us to do so in order to comply with the law or to protect against fraud. We will also release such information:(a) to cooperate with law enforcement or other governmental investigations (without necessarily requiring the law enforcement or government agency requesting the information to formally serve us with a subpoena);
(b) to comply with all valid court orders or subpoenas;
(c) to protect the legal rights of Spelwerx, its employees and our users;
(d) when we believe it is needed for fraud protection and/or credit risk reduction; and/or,
(e) to protect the personal safety of our employees, agents, other users or the public in general.
Spelwerx also reserves the right to report to such entities any activities that we believe to be unlawful. Any such report of the activities outline in (a) thorough (e) will be made without prior notice to you, and you consent to such disclosure by us.
In the event Spelwerx merges with another entity, is acquired by another entity, or enters into a business combination with another entity, Spelwerx may be required to disclose some or all of your personally identifiable information to that entity to continue serving you.
Spelwerx is not in the business of selling, trading or renting personal information. We will not use or share your personally identifiable information with others except those individuals or entities which have a business relationship with Spelwerx.
Children's Privacy
This site is not aimed to attract children and its objective is not to collect personal information from children. Anyone under the age of 18 should not use this site unless supervised by an adult. Spelwerx's goal is to comply with applicable laws and regulations relating to collection and use of information from children, including the Children's On-line Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) of the United States.
Security of Personal Information
The security of your personal identification information is important to us and we aim to protect any such information you may share with us or through us. The third party service providers for Spelwerx use a variety of commercially available security technologies to protect your personally identifying information, including secure servers, firewalls and encryption of financial data, but Spelwerx assumes no responsibility or liability for their effectiveness. Any personal information you provide through Spelwerx, or any link there from, is done so at your own risk.
Bulletin boards, forums and/or newsgroups may also be available to you on or through Spelwerx. Please remember that any information that you provide in these areas becomes public and you should exercise caution in deciding to disclose it.
Your Choices
You can decide whether or not to provide personal information to Spelwerx. However, if you do not provide personal information you may not be able to make purchases, enlist services or access certain offers or options that may be of benefit to you. At the time you provide your information, we will offer you a choice as to whether or not you wish to receive further communications about special offers, product information, or other marketing messages. We may provide this information to our business partners and suppliers. If you choose not to receive these communications, we will not use your personally identifiable information for this purpose.
You may choose to unsubscribe from notices of special offers described in the preceding paragraph. Spelwerx provides you with the ability to unsubscribe at any time by emailing us at remove@spelwerx.com, or by following any "unsubscribe" link.
Changes to this Privacy Statement
Spelwerx may amend this Privacy Statement from time-to-time. We will notify you of such amendments or changes by updating the "Effective Date" at the top of this Privacy Statement.
Spelwerx Contact Information
If you would like to contact us with questions or comments concerning our Privacy Statement or if you feel your inquiry or request has not been addressed to your satisfaction, please contact via e-mail.
